export const questionsData = [
    {
        question: "What is SAAS in full?",
        a: "Service As A Support",
        b: "Software As A Service",
        c: "Software As A Stock",
        d: "Serve As A Server",
        correct: "b",
    },
    {
        question: "Who  invented the compiler?",
        a: "Charles Babbage",
        b: "Bill Gates",
        c: " Grace Hopper",
        d: "Edith Clarke",
        correct: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "Which language is used to provide styling to a website?",
        a: "CSS",
        b: "Java",
        c: "SQL",
        d: "HTML",
        correct: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "What do programmers take as they code?",
        a: "A walk",
        b: "A cup of coffee",
        c: "A beer",
        d: "A chat",
        correct: "b",
    },
    {
        question: "Is web development fun?",
        a: 'Kinda',
        b: 'YES!!!',
        c: 'Um no',
        d: 'IDK',
        correct: "b",
    },
    {
        question: "In what language do computer process it's data?",
        a: "Scala",
        b: "Spanish",
        c: "English",
        d: "Binary",
        correct: "d",
    },
    {
        question: "What does CSS stand for?",
        a: "Central Style Sheets",
        b: "Cascading Style Sheets",
        c: "Cascading Simple Sheets",
        d: "Corrected Sheet Source",
        correct: "b",
    },
    {
        question: "Which language runs in a web browser?",
        a: "Java",
        b: "C",
        c: "Flutter",
        d: "JavaScript",
        correct: "d",
    },
    {
        question: "Which school is best for aspiring software engineers?",
        a: "JKUAT",
        b: "Moringa",
        c: "ALX",
        d: "ICS",
        correct: "b",
    },
    {
        question: "Who among the following is not a technical mentor at Moringa?",
        a: "Rose Oketch",
        b: "Silas Silikhe",
        c: "Newton Bofulo",
        d: "Albert Byrone",
        correct: "c",
    },
];